# Jordan Stewart design • ux • illustration

## About Me\_

Hello! I am Jordan Stewart and I attend Kent State University in Kent, Ohio where I major in Visual Communication Design and minor in User Experience Design. Art, design and coffee are the things that make me get out of bed in the morning. I absolutely love what I do and hope to help as many people as I possibly can through design.

## Contact



#### Email:

istewa61@kent.edu

#### **Phone:**

(440)-610-7789

#### Website:

jordanstewartdesign.com

# Work Experience \_

**Graphic Designer, Kent State Athletics Marketing – 2017–Present** design promotional marketing materials for Kent State Athletics

#### **Supervisor, Common Ground Canopy Tours – 2018**

oversee canopy tour operations, give tours, answer phones, course maintenance

#### Tour Guide, Common Ground Canopy Tours – 2016-2017

give tours to guests, general maintenance, mentor

### Education

#### **Kent State University – Spring 2019**

Bachelor of Fine Arts in Visual Communication Design with a minor in User Experience Design

## **Skills**

#### **Graphic Design, Illustration, User Experience Design**

have completed coursework in typography, graphic design, responsive web design and illustration, and know HTML and CSS

#### Software

Adobe Creative Suite (InDesign, Illustrator, Photoshop, Lightroom, After Effects, Xd), Atom, InVision

## Awards + Achievements

- Featured in the Fall 2017 Kent State VCD Juried Show
- Lorain Arts Council Graphic Design Scholarship
- Kent State Deans List Fall 2015 to Spring 2018
- Eagle Scout